National Congress of Neighborhood Women Records, 1974-1999
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES II. PROGRAMS 1975-1996
  - Leadership
    - Local training
      - Miscellaneous: notes, drafts, and printed material, 1981-84, undated (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - National training
      - General: description and meetings, 1981, undated (Box 112, Folder 10-11)
      - National Leadership Training Conference, 1981 (Box 112, Folder 12)
      - National Leadership training and support group, 1981 (Box 112, Folder 13-22)
      - Network/Leadership program, Rapid City, SD, 1981 (Box 112, Folder 23)
      - National Leadership Conference, Washington, DC, 1982 (Box 112, Folder 24)
      - Leadership training, Harlingen, TX, 1982 (Box 112, Folder 25)
      - National Leadership Training Forum, Douglaston, NY, 1982 (Box 112, Folder 26-32)
      - National Leadership Training Forum, Douglaston, NY (continued), 1982 (Box 113, Folder 1-16)
      - Regional conferences, 1983-85 (Box 113, Folder 17)
      - New York State Neighborhood Women's Leadership Training, Albany, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 18-26)
      - New York State Neighborhood Women's Leadership Training, Albany (continued), 1983 (Box 114, Folder 1-15)
      - Minneapolis training: agenda, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 16)
      - Women Reshaping Communities conference, Syracuse, 1984-85 (Box 114, Folder 17-23)
        [See also Community and economic development]
      - National Leadership Training, Brooklyn, 1988 (Box 114, Folder 24-28)
      - National Leadership Training, Brooklyn, NY (continued), 1988 (Box 115, Folder 1-5)
      - Leadership Training Seminar, Vermont, 1993 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - International Leadership training: Institute, 1989 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Leadership support groups
      - General, 1981, undated (Box 115, Folder 8-11)
      - Manuals and guidelines, 1981, undated (Box 115, Folder 12-14)
      - Handouts (Box 115, Folder 15)
      - Mentor circles questionnaire, undated (Box 115, Folder 16)
      - Williamsburg-Greenpoint Support Group, 1980-83 (Box 115, Folder 17-19)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 115, Folder 20)
    - Subject files
      - General, 1976-84, undated (Box 115, Folder 21-25)
      - Workshops given by other organizations, 1980-84 (Box 115, Folder 26-27)
  - Resource Center
    - General: publicity, descriptions, guide, brochures, lists, and proposals, circa 1978, undated (Box 116, Folder 1-5)
    - Administration: correspondence, meetings, reports, job descriptions, schedule, budget, and miscellaneous notes, circa 1978-81, undated (Box 116, Folder 6-12)
    - Documentation projects
      [See also SERIES I. ADMINISTRATION -Development-WEEA; Leadership video (funded by WEEA); and SERIES V. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS]
      - Douglass St. Productions (NCNW orientation tape): correspondence and budget, 1986 (Box 116, Folder 13)
      - "Ethnic Women as Community Leaders" (Ethnic Heritage Project/Cultural Exchange Project): proposals, description, meetings, report, background, and notes, 1977-80, undated (Box 116, Folder 14-20)
      - "Metropolitan Avenue" film project: proposal, agreement, correspondence and flyer, 1979-85 (Box 116, Folder 21-23)
      - "Working Class Women Changing Their World": description, 1976 (Box 116, Folder 24)
    - Networking: affiliates form, undated (Box 116, Folder 25)
      [See also SERIES I. ADMINISTRATION-Membership; and Public relations]
    - Speakers bureau: publicity, undated (Box 116, Folder 26)
    - Library
      [See also "Resources" under other programs]
      - Audiovisual material: list, guidelines, and resources (Box 116, Folder 27-29)
        [See also SERIES V. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIAL]
      - Bibliographies (Box 116, Folder 30)
      - Bulletin board: flyers and posters (Box 117, Folder 1-3)
      - Community service directories (local) (Box 117, Folder 4-5)
      - Resources and subject files: clippings, articles, printed material, and unpublished papers
        - "Baby M" case (surrogate motherhood) (Box 117, Folder 6)
        - Battered women (Box 117, Folder 7-10)
          [See also SERIES II. PROGRAMS - Women's Survival Space]
        - Black History Month (Box 117, Folder 11)
        - Brooklyn: facts, figures, local history, and maps (Box 117, Folder 12-14)
        - Budgeting (workshop) (Box 117, Folder 15)
        - Business Management
          - General (Box 117, Folder 16-18)
          - "Your Community as Marketplace¼" by NCNW (Box 117, Folder 19)
        - Childcare (Box 118, Folder 1-2)
        - Class
          [See also NCNW]
          - "Expanding Working Class Participation in Women's Conferences" by Shelley Messing (Box 118, Folder 3)
          - "Women Against Women: Middle-Class Bias in Feminist Literature" by Terry L. Haywoode (Box 118, Folder 4)
          - Untitled by Maria Giordano (Box 118, Folder 5)
        - Community development (Box 118)
          [See SERIES II. PROGRAMS-Community and Economic development-Subjects]
        - Disability: "A Few Words on Being Blind" by Charlotte Singer (Box 118, Folder 6)
        - Diversity
          - Dialogue on Diversity: A New Agenda for American Women, 1976 (Box 118, Folder 7)
          - "Women in Planning: Do the Numbers Really Matter?" by Jacqueline Leavitt (Box 118, Folder 8)
        - Economic development (Box 118)
          [See SERIES II. PROGRAMS-Community and economic development-Subjects]
        - Education (Box 118)
          [See SERIES II. PROGRAMS-Education-Resources]
        - Employment (Box 118, Folder 9-15)
          [See also SERIES II. PROGRAMS-Employment-Resources and subject files]
        - Ethnicity
          - "Changing Needs of Ethnic Women in Higher Education," by Laura Polla Scanlon (Box 118, Folder 16)
          - "Dancing the Giglio: An Italian- American Tradition Viewed by Two Generations of Women" (Box 118, Folder 17)
          - "Ethnic Women and the Media," by Christine Noschese (Box 118, Folder 18)
          - "Irish, Italian, and Jewish Women at the Grassroots Level: An Historical and Sociological Perspective," by Kathleen McCourt (Box 118, Folder 19)
          - "Moving Out While Staying Put: Poor Irish Women's Perspectives on Personal Change and Transformation," by Anne T. Rath (Box 118, Folder 20)
        - Family: articles by Elise Boulding and others (Box 118, Folder 21)
        - Grassroots fundraising (Box 118, Folder 22-24)
        - Grassroots organizing
          - "Direct Action Organizing: A Handbook for Women" (Box 118, Folder 25)
          - "A Guide on Networking and Interchange for Grassroots Women," by Barbara B. Stern (Box 118, Folder 26)
          - "How to Include Women Effectively in Your Efforts To Revitalize Neighborhoods," flyer by NCNW (Box 118, Folder 27)
        - Health (Box 119, Folder 1)
        - Homemakers: "The Martha Movement" (Box 119, Folder 2)
        - Housing (Box 119)
          [See SERIES II. PROGRAMS-Housing and tenants--Subject files]
        - Immigrants (Box 119, Folder 3)
        - Leadership (Box 119)
          [See SERIES II. PROGRAMS-Leadership-Resources and Subject files]
        - Legal rights (Box 119, Folder 4)
          [See also SERIES II. PROGRAMS-Miscellaneous projects-Legal project]
        - Library manuals (Box 119, Folder 5-6)
        - Miscellaneous
          - Clippings and flyers (Box 119, Folder 7)
          - "Paper: untitled," by Ied Guinee (Box 119, Folder 8)
          - "The Systems," a story by Darlene McCullough (Box 119, Folder 9)
        - Mothers and daughters: "The Parable of the Mothers and Daughters," by Florence Rush (Box 119, Folder 10)
        - NCNW [See also SERIES I. ADMINISTRATION-Public relations; and SERIES II. PROGRAMS-Community and economic development-Subjects]
          - "The Development of Working-Class Feminism as a Social Movement as Exemplified by the National Congress of Neighborhood Women" (Box 119, Folder 11)
          - The Economic Justice Issue, The Community Development Position of the NCNW (Box 119, Folder 12)
            [See also SERIES II. PROGRAMS-Community and Economic development- Subject files]
          - "I Fight for Everything I Get, And Everything I Get I Fight For...," by Catherine Herman and Marie Leanza (Box 119, Folder 13)
          - "National Congress of Neighborhood Women: Community Uplift Through the Emerging Voice of Women in Poverty," by Janice Peterson and Anne E. Hunter (Box 119, Folder 14)
          - "Women and Neighborhoods: A Case History," by Maria Fava (Box 119, Folder 15)
          - "The Women of Williamsburg: A Report on the National Congress of Neighborhood Women," by Carol Brightman (Box 119, Folder 16)
        - New York City: clipping and report (Box 119, Folder 17-18)
        - New York State
          [See also SERIES II. PROGRAMS-Community and economic development-Dialogues; and Hearings]
          - General: printed material (Box 120, Folder 1)
          - Economic development (Box 120, Folder 2)
          - State Assembly Task Force on Women's Issues (Box 120, Folder 3)
          - NYS Division for Women (Box 120, Folder 4)
          - Women's Issues Task Force, United Way (Box 120, Folder 5)
        - Politics
          - General: printed material (Box 120, Folder 6)
          - NYC politics: clippings (Box 120, Folder 7)
          - "Women's Politics: A Wholistic View" (Box 120, Folder 8)
          - "The Women's Vote Project: An Evaluation," by Ethel Klein (Box 120, Folder 9)
        - Poverty and welfare
          [See also SERIES II. PROGRAMS - Community and Economic development-Subject files]
          - General: clippings (Box 120, Folder 10)
          - "Building Bridges: Women and Economic Justice" (conference) (Box 120, Folder 11)
          - "Public assistance notes" (Box 120, Folder 12)
        - Senior citizens information booklet by NCNW (Box 120, Folder 13)
        - Sexual assault: "Research and Public Hearings Report," NYS Assembly, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 14)
        - Songs (Box 120, Folder 15)
        - Statistics on women (Box 120, Folder 16)
        - Tenants (Box 120)
        - Volunteers (Box 120, Folder 17)
        - Women and philanthropy (Box 120, Folder 18)
        - Women's Fair: "Fact Sheets" on women's resources (Box 120, Folder 19)
        - Women's rights
          - General: clippings and printed material (Box 120, Folder 20)
          - "ERA and Beyond," flyer by NCNW (Box 120, Folder 21)
          - National Women's Conference, Houston, 1977 (Box 120, Folder 22)
          - "National Women's and Women's Rights Organizations," by US Commission on Civil Rights (Box 120, Folder 23)
          - "An Overview of the Women's Movement," by Gloria Steinem (Box 120, Folder 24)
          - "The Women's Movement Must Reclaim the Lost Terrain of Life," by Rasa Gustaitis (Box 120, Folder 25)
          - "Women's Movements and Social Transformations in the Twentieth Century," by Elise Boulding (Box 120, Folder 26)
        - Working class women (Box 120)
          [See Class issues]
  - Women's Public Works
    - General
      - Publicity: newsletter, 1985 (Box 121, Folder 1)
      - Background and goals, 1982-85 (Box 121, Folder 2-3)
      - Orientation, 1985, undated (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1982-87 (Box 121, Folder 5-9)
    - Abt Associates: correspondence, meetings, and miscellaneous, 1982-86 (Box 121, Folder 10-14)
    - Management Information Services (MIS): correspondence and printed material (Box 121, Folder 15-16)
    - Forms, form letters, instructions, and flyers (Box 122, Folder 1-6)
    - Meetings, 1983-84 (Box 122, Folder 7-8)
    - Proposals and background material (Box 122, Folder 9-16)
    - Work plan and revised budget, 1982 (Box 122, Folder 17)
    - Reports
      - NCNW to Rockefeller Foundation, 1983-86 (Box 123, Folder 1-8)
      - Management Information Systems (Abt Associates), 1983-85 (Box 123, Folder 9-13)
      - Management Information Systems (continued): form count and monthly status reports, and miscellaneous, 1984-86, undated (Box 124, Folder 1-3)
      - Manpower (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - Consultant (Simone Charlop) (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Staff: job descriptions (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Women's Survival Space (Center for the Elimination of Violence in the Family)
    - General and miscellaneous, 1977-79, undated (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1977-79 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Board: correspondence, meetings, and lists, 1977-79, undated (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Early planning/Mayor's Task Forces, 1976-77 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - By-laws, undated (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Policies and procedures, 1979, undated (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Reports, 1977-78, undated (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Staff, 1977-79 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Building, 1976-78 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Fundraising, 1977, undated (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - New York State Dept. of Social Services: application for state approval, 1978 (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Resources, 1977, undated (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - Youth Programs
    - Multi-cultural Youth Action program: paper, 1987 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - North Brooklyn Consortium for Adolescent Services, 1985 (Box 126, Folder 2-4)
    - "Raising Children is a Community Thing," Lisel Burns, 1991-92 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Summer Youth programs
      - Summer Youth Fun, 1975 (Box 126, Folder 6-8)
      - Summer Youth Employment Program (Youth Corps) (Box 126, Folder 9-10)
    - Teen Pregnancy program (PRIMA): proposals, 1978-79 (Box 126, Folder 11-12)
      [See also You Can School]
    - You Can Stand on Your Own Two Feet Community School, 1986-
      [See also SERIES I. ADMINISTRATION-Local/NWWG; Development - NYC DOE-JPTA]
      - General: publicity, and newspaper clippings (Box 126, Folder 13)
      - Application (Box 126, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence (Box 126, Folder 15)
      - Meeting (Box 126, Folder 16)
      - Curriculum planning and schedules (Box 126, Folder 17)
      - Courses
        - Starting Fresh with the Environmental Education, 1993 (Box 126, Folder 18)
        - Teen pregnancy prevention, 1988 (Box 126, Folder 19)
        - Theatre Company, undated (Box 126, Folder 20)
      - Database project, undated (Box 126, Folder 21)
    - Four Step Program (S.T.E.P.: Summer Training and Education Program) (Box 126, Folder 23-25)
    - Resources: articles on youth employment (Box 126, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous projects
    - The Corner Store: report, correspondence, forms, and miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Displaced homemakers project, 1970-81 (Box 127, Folder 2-5)
    - Legal Project, 1972-77 (Box 127, Folder 6-12)
    - Worker-owned Cooperative for the Production of Hand-woven Fabrics: proposals, correspondence, printed material, and notes, 1983-84 (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous conferences
    [See also SERIES I. ADMINISTRATION-Annual meetings and conferences; conferences under specific PROGRAMS; and [SERIES III. ORGANIZATIONS]
    - General: conference and workshop schedule, 1985 (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - Community-Based Alternatives and Women in the Eighties (with Women's School of Planning and Architecture), 1980 (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - Educational and Occupational Concerns of White Ethnic Women, undated (Box 127, Folder 16)
    - Housework Conference, undated (Box 127, Folder 17)
    - Neighborhood Platform Conference for Community Women, 1979 (Box 127, Folder 18)
    - Neighborhood "Speakout": Women's Changing Roles in the Family and Community, undated (Box 127, Folder 19)
    - Women's Empowerment: Creating Economic Opportunities for Low-Income Women, Chicago, 1990 (Box 127, Folder 20)
    - Women's Organizing Conference, 1980 (Box 127, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous workshops
    - Anti-rape workshop, undated (Box 127, Folder 22)
    - Business and marketing course, 1981 (Box 127, Folder 23)
    - Classism, undated (Box 127, Folder 24)
    - Self-assessment, 1982, undated (Box 127, Folder 25)
    - Self-improvement, 1975, undated (Box 127, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous: flyers, 1980-82, undated (Box 127, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous events
    - Bicentennial celebration, 1976 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Dinner dance awards nights, 1977, 1979 (Box 128, Folder 2-4)
    - Film screenings, 1980-82, undated (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Housewarming party, 1982 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Labor Theatre, 1980 (Box 128, Folder 7)
      [See also Oversized material]
    - New York Stars basketball game, 1979-80 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Open House: guestbook, 1975 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - 10th Anniversary: "Resolution¼," by NY State Legislature, 1985 (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - General: event planning information and flyers, 1978-80 (Box 128, Folder 11-12)
- SERIES III. ORGANIZATIONS 1974-1991
  - Ad Hoc Coalition on Neighborhoods: printed material, 1980 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Alternatives for Women: printed material, 1981 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - American Association of University Women, Families and Work Project: journal, memo, and printed material, 1982-83 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - American Friends Service Committee ("Women in the Work Force"): printed material, and newsletter, 1980 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - American Planning Association: correspondence, newsletters, clippings, and pamphlets, 1980 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Amnesty International USA, Guatemala Coordination Group: correspondence, 1986 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Association of Junior Leagues: correspondence, newsletters, and printed material, 1980-81 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Association of Neighborhood Housing: correspondence, 1976 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Barnard College Women's Center: correspondence, 1984 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Bank Street College of Education: newsletters and correspondence, 1977-78 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Be Concern Project: printed material, undated (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Bio-Regionalists: meeting notes, 1984 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Bronx Neighborhood Women, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Brooklyn College Women's Center, 1974-84, undated
    - General: correspondence, article, newsletter, printed material, and minutes (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - Crisis Center: correspondence and proposal (Box 129, Folder 15)
    - Peer counseling: proposal (Box 129, Folder 16)
    - Conference: "Women, Culture, and Change: Bridge to a New Era": printed material, reports, miscellaneous, and flyers (Box 129, Folder 17)
  - Brooklyn Community Board Conference: correspondence, article, program, and printed material, 1976-79 (Box 129, Folder 18)
    [See also Williamsburg-Greenpoint Community Planning Board]
  - Brooklyn Educational & Cultural Alliance (BECA): correspondence, clippings, and printed material, 1985-86, undated (Box 129, Folder 19)
  - Brooklyn in Touch: bills, budgets, contracts, correspondence, notes, and printed material, 1980-90, undated (Box 129, Folder 20)
  - Brooklyn Legal Services Corporation: minutes, financial, reports, memoranda, and printed material, 1982-89 (Box 129, Folder 21-22)
    [See also SERIES II. PROGRAMS-Miscellaneous projects-Legal project; SERIES I. ADMINISTRATION-Subject files]
  - Brooklyn Women's Network: correspondence, members list, and minutes, 1980-81 (Box 129, Folder 23)
  - Carroll Gardens Neighborhood Women: correspondence, form, news article, and printed material, 1984-86 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    [See also SERIES II. PROGRAMS-Education-College Program; and Employment-POD]
  - Catholic Guardian Society: annual reports, brochure, and correspondence, 1982-84 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Center for Community Change: correspondence, forms, memos, and printed material, 1980-81 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Center for Neighborhood Technology: brochure, 1985 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Center for Population Activities: printed material, 1981 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Center for Public Advocacy Research, City Women for City Service Project: report, 1984 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Center for Self-Reliant Education: correspondence, 1981 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Center for the Study of Women and Society: flyer, 1984 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Center for Women Policy Studies: notes and printed material, 1979-81 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Child Care, Inc.: correspondence, newsletters, and printed material, 1984-86, undated (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Clearwater: correspondence and newsletters, 1980-81 (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Coalition on Women's Health and Sexuality: conference programs, undated (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Colorado Women's Agenda: newsletter, brochures, and correspondence, 1990-91 (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - "Comadres: Women Empowering Women Through Support and Social Action": flyer, undated (Box 130, Folder 14)
  - Community Development Credit Unions: advertisements, handbooks, clippings, notes, drafts, and printed material, 1983-84, undated (Box 130, Folder 15)
  - Community Renewal Society: correspondence, 1984 (Box 130, Folder 16)
  - Conselyea Street Block Association (and Education Action Center): 1974-90
    - General: cards, meeting announcement, minutes, notes, programs, and report (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Project Giant Step: applications, drafts, forms, flyers, and printed material (Box 130, Folder 18)
  - Consumer Law Training Center: brochure, correspondence, and flyer, 1976-78 (Box 130, Folder 19)
  - The Council of Churches of the City of New York, "Repairing the Breach, 1984 ": correspondence and printed material, 1984 (Box 130, Folder 20)
  - Dolci Task Force: correspondence, flyers, newsletters, and printed material, 1983-84 (Box 130, Folder 21)
  - Eastern Women's Center: flyer, undated (Box 130, Folder 22)
  - Education Center for Community Organizing: budgets, correspondence, flyers, minutes, notes, and report, 1983-84, undated (Box 130, Folder 23)
  - Emergency Alliance for Homeless Families and Children: correspondence, 1986 (Box 130, Folder 24)
  - Families for Action: correspondence and articles, 1978, undated (Box 130, Folder 25)
  - Family Focus Conference, "National Family Resource Forum": brochures, journals, newsletters, and printed materials, 1981 (Box 130, Folder 26)
  - Friends of Woodhull: correspondence, 1981 (Box 130, Folder 27)
  - Girl Scouts of America Conference, "Women are History: Minority Women, Past, Present, Future": correspondence and printed material, 1983 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - "The Governor's Conference on Families": flyer, 1980 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Greater Ridgewood Historical Society: printed material, undated (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Green Party-Institute for Social Ecology conference: brochures, correspondence, journals, meeting notes, newsletters, paper drafts, and printed material, 1983-85, undated (Box 131, Folder 4-7)
  - Greenpoint-Williamsburg Coalition of Community Organizations
    [See also SERIES II. PROGRAMS-Employment-General-School Settlement Association]
    - General: correspondence, flyers, notes, and printed material, 1977-84, undated (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Women's Caucus: memo and membership list, undated (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Greenpoint-Williamsburg District Cabinet (Office of Neighborhood Services, City of New York): meeting notes, 1975 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Guernsey Street Block Association: correspondence, flyers, meeting notes, and printed material, 1983 (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - HealthRight: correspondence, project reports, and printed material, 1978 (Box 131, Folder 12-13)
    [See also SERIES II. PROGRAMS-Employment-POD]
  - Holistic Conscientious Center: correspondence proposals, surveys, and printed material, 1982, undated (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - Human Services Forum: correspondence and printed material, 1982 (Box 131, Folder 15)
  - In Our Own Way: correspondence and printed material, 1986 (Box 131, Folder 16)
  - Institute for Community Economics: correspondence, clippings, newsletters, and printed material, 1984-86 (Box 131, Folder 17)
  - International Women's Year (IWY) (includes New York State Women's Meeting), 1977-84 (Box 132, Folder 1-3)